Can I talk to you?
Who is this to you?
This is your wife.
You were with a woman in the past and she disappointed you.
Yes, sir.
Before you had this woman.
What happened now; it has started now – it is an attack.
It’s true, sir.
When you married this lady, “My honey, my honey”.
Now the affection is not there any more.
It's true, sir.
When you people sit together, people will think you are husband and wife – no affection.
This woman doesn’t even want you to touch her.
It's true, sir.
When you sleep, in the night you will wake up and go sit on the chair.
Prophecy Time
I want to see you.
Go and wait for me.
My name is Mr Chijioke Nwafor
The lady standing by me is my wife - Mrs Nwafor.
We came from Anambra State but we are based in Ekiti State, Nigeria.
Last Sunday, the man of God gave us prophecy.
He said it was God that saved me, that he saw me with a woman in the past who disappointed me.
He said what happened to me with that lady in the past is happening in my marriage now,
that there was no affection in my marriage which was an attack.
So, I confirm the prophecy to be true.
She used to tell me that she wants to quit the marriage; we always fight and quarrel.
Because you don't want her to leave the marriage?
I don’t want her to leave the marriage.
Can you see now?
She wants to leave the marriage and the husband keeps portraying,
"What do you want me to do? You want me to cook for you today? I will cook for you.
You want me to wash your things? I'm ready to wash your clothes."
He has been washing, cooking, doing everything - yet, she still wanted to leave the marriage.
"What else do you want me to do? OK, I will carry you to America for holiday - New York.
After New York we go to London. After London we go to Africa..."
I don't know.
OK, now - I want to quit the marriage.
... because love is from the heart.
Listen to that: she says she wants to quit the marriage after everything he had done.
What is the solution?
Let's listen.
My name is Mrs Ebere Nwafor.
The man standing beside me is my husband.
We came from the Anambra State but we reside in the Ekiti State, Nigeria.
I am a 500 level student of Nnamdi Azikwe University in Akwa.
We have been married for the past one year.
Although I know my husband’s weakness, at a point, I had to call him and sit him down.
I told him the areas he was having weakness
and said we needed to build ourselves up together as one family.
The problem is all about his appearance; I want to start from there.
His appearance does not attract me, although I saw that before I married him.
What attracted me before I married him was his humility and simplicity.
I thought that if I entered the marriage, I would be able to mould him to my taste.
At a point, when we were together, I had to tell my husband that his appearance
was not as it supposed to be.
I told him he was only 35 years old but he dressed like someone who was 70.
I had to be sincere with him, told him to adjust and promised to help him.
No one is perfect.
I said I would mould him to my taste and he too would mould me to his own taste.
However, after we had planned everything, he would take a decision on his own.
At times, when he wanted to visit me in school, I would have to call him on the phone
and tell him what he had to wear because my friends were around.
I told him that he had to look good.
All these are the things which I experienced in marriage which I don’t like or want.
When you were about to get married, was he dressing like this?
He was not actually dressing like this but after the marriage, everything became worse.
His dressing does not attract me.
But before the marriage his look was very good?
He looked more attractive before I married him.
- OK.
- Yes.
Listen to that to learn a lesson.
Those who want to get married - you should dress well, rest...
The SCOAN Sunday Service
After the marriage, no more gym.
The question now is...
Many of you are here today.
The posh car you were using when you wanted to get married - where is it after the marriage?
Does it mean you hired it?
This is what we are talking about.
Listen to her, she is making a point, as well as the gentleman.
We are here to learn.
Man of God, even in the aspect of his body, I have begged my husband to exercise himself.
You asked him to do exercise?
- Yes.
- OK.
I want him to...
Clap for her.
Mr & Mrs Chijioke Nwafor
Prophecy Confirmation
It has really affected my affection for him because after everything, he would agree to do it
but at the end of the day, he wouldn’t do it.
Later on, he would come back to me and start begging me to forgive him but I wouldn’t be happy within me.
I want him to go and do what will bring peace in the house
because whenever I look at him, I am not proud of him.
I want my husband to look good; it is my job to treat him in the way I should but he is not responding.
That is my problem.
Thank you.
But unless the prophecy had come at this time, you would have left the marriage.
Man of God, I must be sincere; I don’t want to leave the marriage.
OK, but you threatened that you wanted to leave?
Yes, but it’s not from my mind.
I don’t want to leave my marriage.
OK, thank you for all this.
I don't need to ask my brother, whatever...
Thank God you have mentioned his age.
The answer you gave me at first - we disagree with it - by saying that you just threatened your husband
about leaving the marriage.
We cannot live above our word.
That is - you cannot live above your word.
Yes.
Satan uses our words to strike.
When you say, "I want to die...", you will soon die.
If I'm talking to you let me see your hand.
What you say out and is in compliance with satan to make it work, "I want to die..." - that is the word of satan -
satan will come and catch you.
"I want to leave my marriage..." - you will see people around and your husband saying it.
There will be people around to get you out of the marriage.
What we are saying now is: love is a thing of the heart.
We know that there is also a need to look good but the major love is a thing of what?
(Heart.)
... is a thing of heart.
Love is a thing of what?
(Heart.)
It is a thing of heart.
Even if your husband dresses now properly and put on the most expensive things -
that love, we are talking about, might not come back any more.
If I'm talking to you let me see your hand.
Even the man raises up his hand.
Clap for Jesus.
Let's assume, my friend - maybe his stomach is big.
It is one of the reasons even if she doesn't want to say that.
She wants him to have a flat one that will look good.
She wants him to wear most expensive clothes.
That love may not be there.
Those things cannot bring love.
Appearance cannot bring the love we are talking about.
Appearance cannot give birth to the love we call marriage.
Tell your neighbour: "There are loves but the love we call marriage - appearance does not produce it".
Tell your neighbour, "There are so many loves but the love we call marriage - appearance does not give it".
The SCOAN Sunday Service
If appearance gives marriage - that marriage cannot stand the test of time.
In a short time crisis or hardship will destroy the marriage.
By appearance...
The love we talk about is love of God.
If appearance is the basis of our marriage or relationship -
such relationship cannot stand the test of time.
Let us look at where the problem is coming from.
Does this marriage come from God?
What is the problem?
If I now say that my brother should go to gym, see doctor, go for a massage, reduce the stomach,
he is too short - he should be higher, and is too fat - he should be slimmer,
his head is too big - he should reduce it, there is too much fat in his hands - they should operate it -
that cannot give that love that will stand the test of time.
Let's look for love.
Tell your neighbour, "Let's look for love somewhere".
Let's look for love somewhere.
Not appearance.
So, I think this is where we are going now.
Deliverance will solve the problem.
The problem we used to have is not the issue of my stature or whatever...
No no no, don't defend yourself.
I'm not defending you.
I am not trying to defend you.
Don't build on my defence.
You can have a separate defence.
Don't talk about the appearance.
I'm only telling you the Word of God.
Lord I want to be like Jesus inner my heart
The SCOAN Sunday Service
The original love, relationship comes from God.
If that relationship is the one that flows through your marriage, it has to do with things of the heart.
Things of the heart are quite different.
Listen, if you because of the things on the outside; appearance, money, position, being handsome,
get married with someone - bet with me; that marriage cannot stand the test of time.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
What has happened to you is what has happened to the sister here.
I only mentioned your situation.
Yours is a disappointment.
The person she intended to marry before disappointed her.
Mr & Mrs Chijioke Nwafor
Prophecy Confirmation
Then she said, "Well, I just need to get married" - that is how she found you.
You have a problem and she has a problem - you need deliverance and she needs deliverance.
Let's assume you were able to find the person you are looking for to marry him from your heart -
this marriage would not exist today.
Let's assume she would be able to be with a person she gave her heart so much to
we would not talk of this marriage.
These two persons have similar problems.
Deliverance and deliverance.
50/50
I will see you people.
Thank you.
The SCOAN Sunday Service